David Rucinski

DATA ANALYST

SUMMARY

Motivated, meticulous, and goal-oriented Data Analyst with proficient knowledge in statistics and experience using statistical packages for analyzing large datasets. Experienced presenting and communicating insights/concepts to both specialists as well as a non-technical audience. Technical expertise regarding data management, database design, data mining and visualization techniques. Strong analytical skills with the ability to organize significant amounts of information with attention to detail and accuracy.

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS

University of Winnipeg

Bachelor of Science in Statistics | June 2019

Coursework: Time Series & Forecasting, Biological Statistics, Statistics in Research, Epidemiology, Applied Multivariate Methods, Applications of Database Systems, Analysis of Variance & Covariance, Statistical Inference

DataCamp - https://www.datacamp.com

Data Scientist with R | Sept. 2019 SQL Fundamentals | Aug. 2019 Data Analyst with R | June 2019

Coursera - https://www.coursera.org/

Machine Learning, Stanford University | May 2019

Maples Collegiate - Joint Red River College

Certificate in Health Care Aide | June 2008

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Health Care Assistant

Riverview Health Centre | Sept. 2008 - Present

- Trained/Proctored HCA students
- Collaborated with healthcare team to meet patient needs

Statistics Tutor

University of Winnipeg | Sept. 2018 - June 2019

- Tutored courses in Mathematics and Statistics
- Communicated in a clear and concise manner with style fitting for the audience
- Organized & created records with MS Access

SKILLS

R / SQL / SAS / Python, Databases, Data Mining, Data Management, Problem Solving, Collaboration, Visuals, Communication, Time Management

PROJECTS

Personal Website | July 2019

- https://davidrucinski.github.io/
- Used Bootstrap 4, HTML, and Markdown to host project output

Crime Statistics in Vancouver | June 2019

- Used R to perform exploratory data analysis on over 600,000 records
- -Created data visualizations & formatted for HTML output

Canadian Unemployment Rates | Apr. 2019

- Performed statistical analysis on a time series data set in R
- Created data visualizations

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

S.P.K Iskry Dance Ensemble | Sept. 2006 - Present

- -Helped at various events: socials, concerts, dinners and fundraisers
- -Performed in various festivals globally

Kapisztrán Hungarian Dance Ensemble | Jan. 2009 - Present

- -Helped at various events: concerts, lunches, and fundraisers
- -Performed at Folklorama and the Western Canadian Hungarian Folk Festivals

CONTACT DETAILS

Email: rucinski.delta@gmail.com Mobile: 204-295-7984 Website: https://davidrucinski.github.io/